<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projectsfolders | Yunming Xiao</title>
    <link>https://yunmingxiao.github.io/projectsfolder/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://yunmingxiao.github.io/projectsfolder/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Projectsfolders</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://yunmingxiao.github.io/img/icon-192.png</url>
      <title>Projectsfolders</title>
      <link>https://yunmingxiao.github.io/projectsfolder/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>FIAT: Frictionless Authentication of IoT Traffic</title>
      <link>https://yunmingxiao.github.io/projectsfolder/fiat/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://yunmingxiao.github.io/projectsfolder/fiat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Home IoT (Internet of Things) deployments are vulnerable to local adversaries, compromising a LAN, and remote adversaries, compromising either the accounts associated with IoT devices or third-party devices like mobile phones used to control the IoT. There is, however, a fundamental difference between an attacker and a legitimate IoT user: the physical interaction with the device (e.g., via a mobile app) used to operate the IoT. This work investigates how this physical interaction can be used to build frictionless IoT traffic authentication. We then design and build FIAT, the first third-party mechanism to automatically authorize IoT traffic by learning recurring traffic and validating human actions behind unpredictable traffic. FIAT does not require modification of the IoT devices or apps, as it operates passively on network traffic. Our evaluation shows that FIAT achieves high accuracy with minimal impact on the user experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- &lt;br&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Resources&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://ringdvpn.com/&#34;&gt;RING: The first multi-vendors bandwidth marketplace&lt;/a&gt; --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Poster&lt;/h3&gt;
Yunming Xiao, Matteo Varvello (2021). &lt;a href=&#34;poster_fiat.pdf&#34;&gt;Poster: FIAT: Frictionless Authentication of IoT Traffic&lt;/a&gt;. In CoNEXT&amp;rsquo;21.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Technical Report&lt;/h3&gt;
Yunming Xiao, Matteo Varvello (2021). &lt;a href=&#34;../../files/frictionless.pdf&#34;&gt;FIAT: Frictionless Authentication of IoT Traffic&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;!-- &lt;h3&gt;Publications&lt;/h3&gt;
... --&gt;
&lt;!-- 1. Marc Anthony Warrior, Yunming Xiao, Matteo Varvello, Aleksandar Kuzmanovic (2020). &lt;a href=&#34;../../publication/dekodi/&#34;&gt;De-Kodi: Understanding the Kodi Ecosystem&lt;/a&gt;. In WWW’20. --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A First Look Into Distributed VPNs</title>
      <link>https://yunmingxiao.github.io/projectsfolder/ring/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://yunmingxiao.github.io/projectsfolder/ring/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ookla reported that average Internet speeds in American homes grew 20x in the last 10 years, from 8 Mbps in2010 to 180 Mbps in 2021, and a similar growing trend isobservable worldwide [8]. Recent studies suggest that the added cost for faster Internet speeds — e.g., $50 monthly to boost from 200 to 300 Mbps with Comcast Xfinity — is not worth to most residential users, which consume only 5% of their available bandwidth. Several systemswere launched which allow users to monetize such spare bandwidth, e.g., distributed proxy or VPN (Virtual Private Network) services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While such systems are attracting a considerable number of users, both as clients (buyers) and providers (sellers), little to nothing is known about such bandwidth marketplaces. We have identified distributed VPN (dVPNs) as the most concrete examples of such marketplaces because, in essence, a dVPN is a system which allows users to sell their spare bandwidth. The contribution of this work is an investigation of the dVPN ecosystem. We run active and passive measurements to characterize their footprint and performance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The analysis of up to six months of dVPNs data shows that  the  three  major  dVPNs  (Mysterium, Sentinel, Tachyon ) compose together a fast-growing network footprint of thousands of nodes (sellers) located all over the world. These nodes offer download speeds comparable with ProtonVPN, a popular centralized VPN. Location-wise, the US is the most attractive market, with the majority of the traffic being destined to services located in the US.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Resources&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://ringdvpn.com/&#34;&gt;RING: The first multi-vendors bandwidth marketplace&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Poster&lt;/h3&gt;
Yunming Xiao, Matteo Varvello, Aleksandar Kuzmanovic (2021). &lt;a href=&#34;poster_ring.pdf&#34;&gt;A First Look Into Distributed VPNs&lt;/a&gt;. In IMC&amp;rsquo;21. &lt;a href=&#34;poster_poster_ring.pdf&#34;&gt;[Poster PDF]&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Publications&lt;/h3&gt;
&amp;hellip;
&lt;!-- 1. Marc Anthony Warrior, Yunming Xiao, Matteo Varvello, Aleksandar Kuzmanovic (2020). &lt;a href=&#34;../../publication/dekodi/&#34;&gt;De-Kodi: Understanding the Kodi Ecosystem&lt;/a&gt;. In WWW’20. --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>De-Kodi &amp; SafeKodi</title>
      <link>https://yunmingxiao.github.io/projectsfolder/dekodi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://yunmingxiao.github.io/projectsfolder/dekodi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Free and open source media centers are currently experiencing a boom in popularity. A complex ecosystem has developed around &lt;a href=&#34;https://kodi.tv&#34;&gt;Kodi&lt;/a&gt;, composed of millions of users, thousands of “add-ons” – Kodi extensions from from 3rd-party developers – and content providers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We developed &lt;a href=&#34;../../publication/dekodi/&#34;&gt;de-Kodi&lt;/a&gt; , a full fledged crawling system capable of discovering and crawling large cross-sections of Kodi’s decentralized ecosystem at tunable levels of depth and breadth. With de-Kodi, we discovered and tested over 9,000 distinct Kodi addons. Our work further serves as the first ever transparent and repeatable analysis of the Kodi ecosystem at large.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Futhermore, on top of de-Kodi, we build a Kodi add-on &lt;a href=&#34;https://safekodi.com&#34;&gt;SafeKodi&lt;/a&gt; which helps to protect Kodi users from malacious Kodi add-ons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A nice video to demonstrate the usage of SafeKodi:
&lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/9outnVKMQ1E&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Resources&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://safekodi.com/&#34;&gt;SafeKodi: The first aggregator for (safe) Kodi addons&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Publications&lt;/h3&gt;
1. Marc Anthony Warrior, Yunming Xiao, Matteo Varvello, Aleksandar Kuzmanovic (2020). &lt;a href=&#34;../../publication/dekodi/&#34;&gt;De-Kodi: Understanding the Kodi Ecosystem&lt;/a&gt;. In WWW’20.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Media Coverage&lt;/h3&gt;
1. &lt;a href=&#34;https://torrentfreak.com/safekodi-researchers-help-kodi-users-to-spot-malicious-addons-200306/&#34;&gt;SafeKodi: Researchers Help Kodi Users to Spot Malicious Addons - TorretFreak.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
2. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.technadu.com/safekodi-save-users-from-risky-kodi-addons/94748/&#34;&gt;“SafeKodi” is Here to Save Users From Risky Kodi Addons - TechNadu.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
3. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.express.co.uk/life-style/science-technology/1252981/Kodi-update-news-stream-warning-alert&#34;&gt;Why streaming on this TV player just got a lot less dangerous - Daily Express&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
4. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.adslzone.net/noticias/seguridad/safekodi-primer-antivirus-kodi/&#34;&gt;Crean el primer antivirus para Kodi: protégete de addons con malware - AdslZone.net&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
5. &lt;a href=&#34;https://pplware.sapo.pt/software/safekodi-acabaram-se-os-addons-maliciosos-no-kodi/&#34;&gt;SafeKodi: Acabaram-se os addons maliciosos no Kodi - Pplware.sapo.pt&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
6. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.pcsteps.gr/331074-safekodi-%cf%80%cf%81%ce%bf%cf%83%cf%84%ce%b1%cf%83%ce%af%ce%b1-%ce%ba%ce%b1%ce%b9-%ce%b1%cf%83%cf%86%ce%b1%ce%bb%ce%ad%cf%82-streaming-%cf%83%cf%84%ce%bf-kodi/&#34;&gt;SafeKodi: Προστασία Και Ασφαλές Streaming Στο Kodi v18.6 - PcSteps.gr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
7. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.vpncompare.co.uk/new-kodi-tool-safe/&#34;&gt;The new Kodi tool that helps keep streamers safe - VPNCompre.co.uk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
8. &lt;a href=&#34;https://yeeeah.fr/tech/safekodi-les-chercheurs-aident-les-utilisateurs-de-kodi-a-reperer-les-modules-malveillants&#34;&gt;SafeKodi: les chercheurs aident les utilisateurs de Kodi à repérer les modules malveillants - Yeeeah.fr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
9. &lt;a href=&#34;https://vpnbasen.se/forskargrupp-har-tagit-fram-safekodi-en-app-letar-efter-skadliga-tillagg/&#34;&gt;Forskargrupp har tagit fram ”SafeKodi” – en app letar efter skadliga tillägg - VPNBasen.se&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
10. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.fredzone.org/safekodi-pour-eviter-les-extensions-verolees-sur-kodi-288&#34;&gt;SafeKodi, pour éviter les extensions vérolées sur Kodi - FredZone.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
11. &lt;a href=&#34;https://troypoint.com/safekodi/&#34;&gt;Is Your Kodi Virus Free? Use SafeKodi to Scan &amp;amp; Fix - TroyPoint.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
12. &lt;a href=&#34;https://troypoint.com/safekodi/&#34;&gt;SafeKodi: O maior aliado de quem usa o Kodi - NoticiasETecnologia.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;More videos&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xCW_2v1vkWM&#34;&gt;Is Your Kodi Virus Free? How to Scan With SafeKodi - TROYPOINT Vids&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tLxmJLcaZq4&#34;&gt;KODI 2020*NOVEDAD PARA KODI*EL ANTIVIRUS!! - tutvboxaldia kodi&amp;amp;Android&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
